Uh asalam alaikum everyone. Uh today I
would like to introduce credential
insurance. So, Credential is an
insurance company that provide health
insurance to help people protect themsel
and their family. Uh, and it offer
financial support during unexpected
situation such as accident and illness.
And by having insurance, individual can
uh for a safer and more secure future uh
without worrying too much about high
medical costs. Next, I will explain one
of the prudential health insurance
policies which is BRU millionm 2.0. PRU
millionm 2.0 is a medical insurance plan
that help pay for hospital and medical
treatment cost and one of its main
benefit uh is that it provide high
annual coverage with no lifetime limits
and this mean uh the coverage renew
every year as a result policy holder can
reduce the financial burden caused by
medical expenses due to illness or
accident. Another health insurance
policies offered by credential is PRU
value m designed for long-term
protection. It helped cover hospital and
treatment cost and continue to provide
support even after reaching its lifetime
limit paying part of future medical
expenses. This make PRU value M suitable
for individual who want to manage high
medical cost over a long period of time.
Okay. Next, the scope of coverage
provide by PRU Mill and PU value M. This
policy focus on medical protection and
helps cover high medical expenses.
First, the policy cover hospitalization
and surgery. This mean is pay for
hospital room charge, daily medical
treatment and surgical procedure when
you are admitted to the hospital. Next,
the policy also cover ICU treatment. If
the patient is in critical condition and
needs intensive care, the policy will
cover the ICU cost without a fixed limit
on the numbers of day. In addition, P
media M provide cancer treatment
coverage including chemotherapy, radio
and other advanced cancer treatment
which can be very expensive. The policy
also cover pre and post hospitalization
treatment. This include medical checkup
before hospital admission and follow-up
treatment after discharge. Lastly, PR
million offer a high annual coverage
limit of up to 8 million per year
depending on the plan chosen which help
protect individual from high medical
cost. So next is our benefit. The
benefit discussed in this session are
based on selected credential health
insurance product namely PRU million m
2.0 O and PRU value map as they present
the core medical benefit offered by
prudential Malaysia. So the first one is
comprehensive coverage with no lifetime
limit. This mean there is no maximum
limit on claim throughout policy holders
lifetime and giving long-term financial
protection. So next is recover
comfortably. This plan helps policy
holders to recover comfortably by
providing hospital room and board
coverage from 200 ringit to 400 ringit
per day only. It is also covers up to
150 days of hospital stay in a year. And
next is comprehensive cancer protection.
This includes genomic testing, cancer
treatment and follow-up care even during
the cancer remission period. So next is
comprehensive coverage with special
lifetime limit. This plan provide wide
medical coverage but with a special
lifetime limit that have been fed. This
means the coverage is comprehensive.
However, there is a maximum amount that
can be claimed over the policy holders
lifetime. Next is recover comfortably
which is same as before which they
provide hospital room and board up to
200 to 400 ringgit and it's cover up to
150 days a year and last one is extend
medical coverage overseas. It provides
extra protection that also can be used
outside the Malaysia which is very
useful when traveling or staying abroad
because we don't know when we will use
this insurance. Thank you.
>> This slide explain the execution policy
of the insurance plan. First, only
medically necessary and reasonable
treatment are covered. Optional or
non-essential treatment are not covered.
Next, treatment done outside the allowed
time period either before or after
hospitalization. In addition, any claim
that except the annual or lifetime limit
will not be paid for emergency assistant
and second medicinal opinion. These
service are provided by third parties
and are not part of the insurance
policy. Alternative treatment are not
covered under selected plans and within
specific limit. Lastly, preventive care
benefit apply only if no claim was made
in the previous year. So here is the
reason to consider potential health
insurance. Firstly, medical costs today
are very expensive and continue to
increase which can be financial burden
for many people. Therefore, provincial
health insurance provide coverage for
hospitalization and medical treatment to
help manage these high medical expenses.
This policy also help to reduce the
financial burden during the illness or
accident especially when unexpected
medical situation happen. At the same
time, it protects individuals and their
families from financial stress caused by
medical bills. Overall, financial health
insurance give peace of mind and
long-term protection allowing people to
focus on recovery without worrying about
their finance. Thank you. First of all,
for the link section, all the links are
taken from Predential official website.
Next, the official website link is used
for general information about Predential
and the product offer. Then PRU media
map and PRU where you met links explain
the policy details and the benefit of
coverage. Lastly, the medical claims
form link is used when customer wants to
make a hospital treatment clips.